SUMMARY

Enterprising and industrious business in technology services and telecommunications services. Professional with demonstrated success at proposing and selling technology devices, plans and services for cell phones, tablets, home phone, internet, TV and home automation.

Effectively research and learn new and ever- changing technologies and communicate clearly to customers and potential customers. Successfully analyze and problem solve customer and technological issues.

- Sales presentation & closing
- Facility with new technologies
- Customer service delivery skills
- Effective team member
- Creative problem solving
- Exceptional communication skills

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

AT&T Corporate Retail, Seattle, WA Retail Sales Consultant June 2014 – May 2018 propose and sell technology devices, plans and services for cell phones, tablets, home phone, internet, TV (DIRECTV) and home automation.

- Introduced new phone and telecommunication products and services to customers; provided exceptional education and knowledge in support of sales.
- Effectively researched and learned new and ever- changing technologies and accessories to communicate and sell to customers.
- Established business sales relationships to facilitate future sales opportunities.
- Analyzed cell phone plan details; summarized and presented pertinent information to current and future customers.
- Communicated clearly and provided excellent customer relations.
- Effectively analyzed and problem solved customer and technological issues.
- Consistently met and exceeded customer satisfaction metric of 80% or higher and frequently attain 95% to 100%.
- Met aggressive metric by adding additional business lines on a consistent basis.

Leading Edge Academy, Mesa, AZ

Elementary Educator 2009- 2014

Responsibility for all preparation and delivery of academic curriculum for elementary grade classes at this "A +" Charter School.

- Effectively collaborated with staff, students, parents and school officials to achieve learning goals.
- Instituted effective time management for meeting needs of 20-30 students.
- Conducted presentations to staff and families utilizing effective technology.
- Utilizing technology such as Smart Boards, provided effective computer instruction.

Wilson District Public School, Phoenix, AZ Elementary Educator 2008 - 2009

Overall responsibility for preparation and delivery of academic curriculum for fourth grade classes in this Title 1 school.

- Collaborated with team members and families to solve learning problems.
- Dealt effectively with challenging student behaviors and obstacles to learning.
- Planned and delivered multi-level instruction to a diverse student population.
- Communicated effectively with Spanish speaking families.

Northern Arizona University, Flagstaff, AZ Testing Coordinator 2005 – 2007 Managed and monitored a safe and efficient testing center for students with disabilities.

- Conducted research on new assistive technologies and computer programs.
- Managed confidential personal documents for various school departments.
- Acted as Lead Office Assistant; directed phone calls, ensured orders were correct, and maintained a database of students.

EDUCATION / TRAINING

Bachelors of Science, Elementary Education & Teaching

Northern Arizona University, Flagstaff, AZ

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

The Carroll School, Lincoln, MA –Symphony Mathematics Applied Behavioral Analysis - ABA Instructor Program Special Education - International Dyslexia Conference